〈（純一）２年前のクリスマスイブ〉
Two years ago, on Christmas Eve...
I gave up on waiting for her to show up,
〈来ない彼女を待つのを
あきらめた僕は〉
and was about to go home alone.
〈一人　家へ帰ろうとしていた〉
〈来るときには予想もしなかった
寂しい気持ちが〉
I couldn't have imagined this
crushing loneliness on my way here.
〈押し寄せていた〉
〈僕…　フラれたのかな？〉
Was I... rejected?
〈明日　学校で会ったら彼女に
どんな顔をすればいいんだろう〉
I don't know how I'll face her at school tomorrow.
うッ
What are you doing?
（薫）何してんの？
薫！
Kaoru!
What are you doing here?
何で　こんなところにいるの？
Don't tell me someone stood you up?!
もしかして
誰かに　すっぽかされちゃった？
Y-You're wrong.
ちッ　違うよ
ねえ　送ってよ
Hey, give me a ride.
I was just about to go pick up a Christmas cake.
クリスマスケーキを
取りに行くところなんだ
うちはね　毎年　お母さんと二人で
Every year, my mom and I have a Christmas party together.
クリスマスパーティー　やることになっててさ
Oh?
へえ
I know!
そうだ
よかったら　うちに来ない？
Wanna come over to my place?
ケーキ　二人じゃ食べきれないから
My mom and I can't finish the cake with just the two of us.
You can have the leftovers.
残ったら
食べさせてあげてもいいわよ
えッ？
いいから
What?
Whatever, just give me a ride to the bakery.
ケーキ屋さんまでは送ってよ
You can decide whether you want to come or not on our way there.
来るか来ないかは
その間に決めればいいでしょ？
O-Okay.
あッ…　ああ
All right.  Let's go!
ほら　レッツゴー！
I love you from my heart
・～
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
（寝息）
うわ～ッ！
あははは…
いいよ　いいよ　そのリアクション
Yes, yes!  What a reaction!
何だ　薫か
O-Oh, it's you, Kaoru.
いきなり人の耳　かむなよ！
Don't just suddenly bite my ear!
むふ～　気持ちよかった？
Did it feel good?
ふんッ　大したことないよ
It wasn't anything special.
Here, if you like biting so much, go ahead and bite this ear too.
ほら　かめるもんなら
こっちも　かんでみろよ
うわ～ッ！
D-Don't actually bite it!
ホ…　ホントにかむなよ！
Didn't you tell me to?
かんでみろって言ったじゃない
確かに言ったけど
普通　かまないだろ？
I did, but you don't normally do that!
I can, because of the relationship we have.
いいじゃない
あんたと私の仲なんだから
In other words, because we're strangers.
つまり　他人ってことだよな
うわ～　そこまで言う？
Whoa, you'd really go that far?
Yep.
うん
そう…　じゃあ
これで　さよならね
I see.
Then I guess this is farewell.
うん
思い返せば　はや～
Yeah.
When I think back on it, it's been such a short...
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 1
Buddy
はや…
中学の頃からだから３年だな
Such a short...
We've known each other since middle school, so three years.
そそそ　３年
衝撃的な出会いを果たした二人は
That's right, three years!
The two of us met with a bang and brought our relationship to fruition...
果たしてないよな
No we didn't.
（梅原）いよ～　大将
また夫婦漫才か？
Sup, boss?  Married couple stand-up comedy again?
Obviously not!
そんなのじゃないよ！
もう　冷たいんだから
Geez, don't be so cold.
・（梅原）棚町も大変だな
You must be having it tough too, Tanamachi.
大変なのは僕の方だ
I'm the one who has it tough!
It's fine, Umehara-kun.
いいのよ　梅原君
私が好きで　やってることだから
I do this because I like it.
ク～　けなげだ　泣けるぜ！
How brave.  I could cry!
Yes, you can call me the bravest and prettiest girl in town.
ええ　けなげ小町と呼んでも
よろしくてよ
Oh yeah, Umehara-kun.  Maybe you'll know about it.
そうだ
梅原君なら知ってるかな？
バイト先とかで
話題になってるんだけど
I've been hearing about it at my part-time job.
最近　できたポートタワーって
もう行った？
Have you been to the newly-finished Port Tower?
クーッ　棚町
切ない質問をするじゃねえか
Tanamachi, that's a painful question you're asking.
あんなデートスポット
一人で行けねえよ
There's no way I could go to that date spot alone!
そうなの？　何か
水族館とか展望台とかあって
Really?
They have an aquarium and viewing platform there.
楽しいらしいじゃない
Doesn't it sound fun?
ねえ　みんなで一緒に行かない？
Hey, how about we all go together?
みんなって　俺ら３人ってことか？
うん
Together?  You mean, all three of us?
Yeah.
まあ　デートで行きてえところだが
Well, it's a place I'd rather go to for a date,
背に腹は代えられねえな
but I guess I'll have to give up on that.
Yeah, I could just look at it as checking the place out.
うん　下見ということで
行くのもありか…
Yep.
うん　うん
決まり！
It's decided!
Then when should we go?
じゃあ　いつにする？
行かない
I'm not going.
（梅原・薫）えッ！
あんなところ　つまんないよ
What?
That place sounds boring.
どうした　大将？
どうせ　カップルばっかだし
What's the matter, boss?
There's only gonna be couples there anyway.
僕達が行ったって
うきまくるだけだよ
We're just gonna feel left out if we go.
そんなの　行ってみないと
分かんないでしょ
You don't know that for sure unless you go!
I'm pretty sure there'll be families there.
他の家族連れだって
多分　いるわよ
ねえ　あなた
てッ
Come on, darling.
We're not family!
僕達　家族じゃないだろう！
（詞）梅原君達
そろそろ授業が始まるから
Umehara-kun and Tanamachi-san, class is about to start,
席に　ついてくれないかな
so could you please take your seats?
Oh, I'm sorry.
おお　悪い
Geez, she's so strict.
たく　おカタいんだから
ねえ？
まあ　そう言うなよ
Right?
Don't say that.
絢辻さんにも　クラス委員って
立場があるんだからさ
Ayatsuji-san has to fulfill her role as the class rep.
あん　どっちの味方なのよ！？
Ugh, who's side are you on?!
うわ～ッ
Sorry, are you okay?
ごめん　大丈夫！？
パッ　パッ　パンチ
P-P-Pan...
Punch?
パンチ？
You dodged my right hook pretty well.
よく　よけたよね
私の右フックを
ああ…　パンチラ
Panties...
あッ？
You idiot!
て　バカッ！
うッ…
Junichi, you're awake?
純一　気づいた？
あれ？
Huh?
僕　どうして保健室に？
Why am I in the infirmary?
覚えてないの？
You don't remember?
さっぱり記憶が…
I don't remember anything...
こッ　転んだのよ
それで頭とおなかを打って
Y-You fell over and hit your head and stomach.
そう　それで
薫がここまで運んでくれたのか？
I see.  You brought me all the way here then, Kaoru?
そうそう　感謝しなさい
ふふふ
That's right, be thankful!
うそをつけ
お前が殴ったんだろう！
Liar!  You're the one who hit me!
何だ…　バレバレか
Oh, so you knew.
まったく
ちょっとは手加減しろ
Geez, you didn't have to hit me that hard.
寸止めしたわよ
でも　あんたが当たっちゃうから
I stopped right before I hit you!
But you just happened to get hit.
それは寸止めとは言わないだろ
You can't say that you stopped then!
Ow...
イテテ
大丈夫？
A-Are you okay?
ああ…
S-Sorry.
ごめん
えッ？
ホント　ごめんなさい
I'm really sorry.
もしかして
ずっと　ついててくれたのか？
Don't tell me... you've been with me the whole time?
まあ　そんなとこ
Yeah, pretty much.
怒ってるでしょ？
Are you mad?
I can't get mad at you if you make that face.
そんな顔されたら怒れないだろ
もういいよ
It's fine.
But...
でも…
いいって
I said it's fine.
You did hit me, but... well...
殴られはしたけど　その…
I got to... see yours, Kaoru...
薫の…　見せてもらったし
はッ？
でもまあ　そういうことだから
Anyway, that's how it is, so let's call it even.
イーブンってことで
You were worried for me, right?
心配してくれてたんだろ？
うん　それはね
Yeah, I was.
お前に
心配してもらえることなんて
There haven't been many times when you've worried about me.
ほとんど　なかったからな
I don't really think so...
そうでもないと思うけど
Either way, it's still rare for you to do that.
どっちにしろ
珍しいのは確かだろ？
まあ　そうかもね
Well, I guess so.
It brought back memories.
思い出してたんだよね
何を？
Of what?
中学の頃も
こうして二人して保健室で
When we were in middle school, we
skipped class in the infirmary just like this.
サボったこと　あったでしょ？
覚えてる？
Do you remember?
No.
いや　あのときも今も
I wasn't the one skipping class back then, and I'm not now.
僕は　サボりじゃなかったけどな
細かいことはいいじゃない
Don't worry about little details like that!
はあ…　薫は変わらないよな
Kaoru, you haven't changed at all.
You've been unpredictable since middle school.
中学の頃から
メチャクチャなことばっかして
「輝日東の核弾頭」なんて
あだ名までついちゃって
You even earned yourself the nickname "Warhead of Kibitou".
その名で呼ばないでよ
Don't call me that.
Sorry.
すみません
Well, I'm going.
さて　もう行くね
Okay.
ああ
閉めとく？
Want me to close the curtains?
うん
じゃあ　お大事に
Yeah.
Well then, take care!
て　お前が言うなよ！
Wait, I don't want you telling me that!
おおッ！
肝心なこと　言い忘れてた
I forgot to tell you something important.
ああ　何？
What?
Come to the flower beds at the
back of the campus after school.
放課後
校舎裏の花壇のところに来て
えッ？
必ず　来るのよ
You have to come.
ああ…　何だったんだ？　今の
What was that all about?
（ドアが閉まる）
何で　わざわざ放課後に
Why would she go out of her way to tell me to go to a deserted place after school?
人けのない校舎裏に
呼び出すんだ？
薫が僕に告白！？
Kaoru's gonna confess to me?!
いやいや　ないだろう
No, no way.
ない…　ってことは
Which means...
《（ゴング）》
《輝日東の核弾頭で
のるかってんだ！》
Sucks for you that I'm the "Warhead of Kibitou"!
No, she wouldn't need me to go to the back of the campus for that.
いや　それなら
校舎裏じゃなくてもいいだろう
てことは！
Which means...
《純一！》
《薫》
Junichi!
K-Kaoru!
《来てくれたのね》
You came!
《好き～》
I love you!
《あははは》
《純一…》
Junichi...
まさか！　あいつとは
中学のときからの悪友なんだぞ
No way!
She's been a buddy of mine since middle school!
For that to happen now...
それを　今さら…
No, no, no!
いやいやいや
But she was really worried for me just then...
でも　さっきだって
あんなに心配してたし
もしかして！？
Could it be...
《何だ　これ？》
What's this?
《お帰りなさい　あなた》
Welcome home, dear.
《ご飯にします？》
Will you have dinner?
《おふろにします？》
Will you take a bath?
Or will you...
《それとも…》
うわ～ッ！
（響）ちょっと　静かにしてくれる？
寝てる子がいるの→
Hey, could you keep it down?
Someone's asleep.
ここ　保健室なのよ
This is an infirmary, you know.
（はるか）うんん…
はッ　はい　すみませんでした
O-Okay.
I-I'm sorry!
（麻耶）江戸時代に
とても正確な日本の地図を→
Inou Tadataka became known for his very
accurate map of Japan during the Edo period.
製作したことで知られる
伊能忠敬は→
Does anyone know how he made it?
どのようにして
地図を作ったか分かりますか？
（鼻歌）
わッ！
梨穂子！
Rihoko!
（梨穂子）ああ　純一！
Ah, Junichi!
Here.
ほれ
ありがとう
Thanks.
で…　ごめんね
I'm sorry.
僕こそ
ちょっと　ぼんやりしてたから
Me too.  I wasn't paying attention.
あれ？　何か純一　顔が赤いよ
Huh?
Junichi, your face is all red.
えッ　いや…　そうか？
What?  Uh... really?
熱があるんじゃない？
Do you have a fever?
いや　大丈夫だから…
No, I'm fine.
う～ん…　ないかなあ
Hmm... you don't.
By the way, what are you doing out here?
というか
こんなとこで何してるんだよ？
ああ　今日ね　茶道部のＯＧが
来ることになってて
Um... some graduated members of the
Tea Club are coming today, so my seniors...
先輩達に…
どうした？
ヤダ！
What's wrong?
Oh no!  I forgot what I came here to do!
私　何しにここに来たのか
忘れちゃったかも
はあ？
大変！
What?!
This is bad!
Don't trip, Rihoko!
転ぶなよ　梨穂子！
うん！
Okay!
わあ～
あいつ　大丈夫かな？
I wonder if she'll be okay.
いや　今は梨穂子より自分のことだ
Wait, I gotta worry about myself first.
あッ　あの角を曲がったら…
O-Once I go around that corner...
Go around that corner...
角を　曲がったら…
Junichi.
《純一　実は私》
I actually like...
《あんたのこと…》
はあ～
Ah, Tachibana-kun.
（恵子）あッ　橘君
純一？
Junichi?
どうしたの？
What's the matter?
〈何で田中さんが　いるんだ？〉
Why is Tanaka-san here?
Hey, are you listening?
ねえ　聞いてる？
だから　今から恵子の話を
しっかり聞いて
You're supposed to hear what Keiko has to say and give your opinion.
あんたの意見を言ってみて
うん？
だから　あんたは校内の男子代表に
選ばれたって言ってるの
I'm saying I chose you to represent all the boys in this school.
う～ん…　て言われても
Well, I don't know about that...
ごめんね　橘君
I'm sorry, Tachibana-kun.
謝ることなんて　ないない
There's nothing to apologize to this moron about.
このボンクラに
ボンクラって…
Moron, huh?
校内男子代表って言ったり
ボンクラって言ったり
First you say I represent the boys in this school, then you call me a moron.
Which one am I?
どっちかにしてくれない？
あははは
ホントだよね　橘君も大変だね
It's true.  You also have it tough, Tachibana-kun.
You too, Tanaka-san.
田中さんもね
もう慣れちゃった　へへへ
I'm used to it.
ははは…
何二人で意気投合してるのよ
What's with this mutual understanding between you two?!
恵子　早く本題を言いなさい
Keiko, hurry up and hit the main subject!
（恵子）えっと　私ね→
Um...
Well, I confessed to a guy in our class.
クラスの　ある男の子に告白したの
ええッ？　そういう話なんだ
So that's what you wanted to talk about.
Whatever, just hear her out.
いいから　とりあえず聞きなさいよ
うん
Okay.
それで　私　その人に返事は少し
待ってくれって言われたから
He then told me to wait for his answer,
しばらく待ってたんだけど
so I waited for a while...
しばらくって？
一ヵ月くらいよね
For how long?
Probably around a month.
えッ　一ヵ月も？
うん
For a month?!
Yes.
何ていうか
恵子ってホント　レアものだよね
How should I put it...
There aren't many girls like you, Keiko.
普通　そんなに待たないって
A typical person wouldn't wait that long.
あはは…
うんでもって
Though, when he finally asked for her, that happened.
やっと呼び出してきたと思ったら
あれだったんでしょ？
What happened?
「あれ」？
そう　そいつ恵子に
Yes, what do you think he said to Keiko?
何て言ったと思う？
I have no idea.
う～ん
そんなの見当もつかないよ
He said, "let me kiss you".
キスさせろだってさ
バカにするのも
いい加減にしろっての
Even if you're making fun of someone, you shouldn't go that far!
えッ　キス！
ろくに返事もしないで
A kiss?!
He doesn't give her an answer and
leaves her alone, then he asks for a kiss ?!
放っておいて　何がキスよ
そッ　それで
田中さんは　どうしたの？
S-So Tanaka-san, what did you do?
キスしたの？
Did you kiss him?
ううん　まさか
No, I didn't.
さすがに　そのときは断ったけど
もう一度言われたら…
I turned him down then, but if he asks me again...
And so we're just thinking about what to do.
で　どうしよっかってとこなの
なるほどね
I see.
I'm sorry for asking you for weird advice.
（恵子）ごめんね　ヘンな相談で
No, I don't mind...
ううん　それは構わないけど…
Well then, as the representative of the boys in this school,
そういうわけで　全校の男子代表
hurry up and give us your opinion.
手っとり早く　意見を述べなさい
意見って言われてもな～
まあ　私の予想は
I don't know about my opinion...
Well, I predict that he'll end up making Keiko cry.
恵子が泣かされる　はめになるって
感じなんだけど
へえッ！
おいおい　何もそうズバッと…
What?!
Hey now, you didn't have to be so blunt.
私の予想は　どうでもいいの！
My prediction doesn't matter!
So let's hear what you think!
いいから
あんたの意見を言いなさいよ！
えッ　う～ん　そうだなあ
Let's see.
手紙を出してみるとか
Why don't you write him a letter?
手紙？
なーんか地味ね
A letter?
That's pretty lame.
Isn't there an easier way to solve this?
もっと
さっくり解決する方法ないの？
If there's an easier way, you
wouldn't need me in the first place.
さっくり解決するようなら
僕に聞かなくても解決するだろ？
Yeah, you're right.
うん…　確かにそうね
でも手紙ったって　何て書くのよ？
But what are we gonna write in the letter?
う～ん
ちゃんと返事してくれるのを
待ってますとか
Something along the lines of,
"I'm still waiting for a proper reply"?
そういう感じは？
Since you already confessed to him before,
一度　告白してるのなら
しつこくするより
I think you should take a more indirect approach instead of being persistent.
間接的にいった方が
いいと思うんだ
直接会って
またキスさせろって言われても
He might ask you to kiss him again if you meet him directly, and we don't want that.
困るだろうしね
一理あるわね
You have a point.
Keiko, well?
恵子　どう？
うん　早速やってみる
Okay, let's try that.
橘君　ありがとう
Tachibana-kun, thanks.
ははッ　どういたしまして
You're welcome.
なあ　薫
うん？
Hey, Kaoru.
さっきの田中さんの相手って
誰なんだ？
Who's that guy Tanaka-san was talking about?
Well, it's not something I can just tell anyone about.
さあね　私が
とやかく言うことじゃないわ
それもそうだな
I guess not.
田中さん　うまくいくといいな
I hope things work out for Tanaka-san.
I intend to do what it takes for that to happen too.
そうなるように　私も動くつもりよ
おッ？
余計なことは　するなよ
Don't overdo things.
Don't worry.
大丈夫だって
これ以上に　ないくらい
I'll make it all so perfect, it won't get any better.
バッチリうまく　まとめるから
No.  Every time you say "perfect", it's always something destructive.
いや　お前のその
バッチリっていうのは
いつも
破壊的な方向にいってるだろ？
そうかな？
そうかなじゃないだろう
Really?
What do you mean, "really"?
あッ　ヤバッ
私　今日バイトだった
Crap, I have work today!
バイトって
まだ　あの駅前のファミレスか？
You're still working at that family restaurant by the train station?
そそそ　今さ　お店で冬の
味覚フェアってのをやってるのよ
Yup.  We're doing a Winter Flavors fair right now.
冬の味覚フェア？
Winter Flavors fair?
そうそう　それで
カニの殻にグラタンを入れたりしててさ
That's right.  We're putting gratin in crab shells and stuff.
へえ　それは　おいしそうだな
Ooh, that sounds delicious.
揺れるし　滑るし
運ぶのが大変なのよ
It wobbles and it's slippery.  Carrying it around is tough!
「北からきたカニグラタン」　とか
Like the "Crab From The North Gratin",
「エノキダケだっけ和風パスタ」　とか
or the "Full Enogi Mushroom Japanese-style Pasta".
くっだらないダジャレの名前
つけてさ
They have names with really lame puns.
They're pretty lame, yeah.
微妙なダジャレだな
"Understood!  You want a 'Crab From The North Gratin', is that right?"
「かしこまりました！　北からきた
カニグラタンでございますね」　って
Repeating the order is embarrassing!
注文の繰り返しが
恥ずかしいっての
ああ　そりゃ確かにおかしいわ
Yeah, I guess that is kinda weird.
あ～あ　別のバイト　探そうかなあ
Should I look for another part-time job?
ファミレス以外で
やってみたいバイトってあるのか？
Have you tried looking for a job that isn't in a family restaurant?
うん　いっぱいあるわよ
Yeah, lots of them.
遊園地のアトラクションのお姉さんとか
An assistant at an attraction in a theme park, for example.
ああ　それは何だか楽しそうだな
That sounds kinda fun.
でしょう？
でも倍率が厳しそうでさ
I know, right?
But the competition seems fierce...
Don't worry, you'd make it for sure.
大丈夫　お前なら受かるよ
そう？　テンキュ
Really?
Thank you.
Sign: For pedestrians and bikes
なあ　バイトって
何がおもしろいの？
Hey.
What's fun about a job?
うん？　お金が入るところ
えッ？
You get money.
あはは…　冗談
Just kidding!
でも　半分本気
Though, that's half-true.
I mean, it's just me and my mom at home.
だってほら
うち母一人　娘一人じゃない？
だから　お母さんと二人で
頑張ってやっていこうって
That's why my mom and I
promised each other we'd work hard.
約束してるわけ
I see.
ああ　そうだったね
（美也）逢ちゃん　残念だったね
What a shame Ai-chan couldn't come.
（紗江）しかたないよ　部活だもん
Nothing we could do about it.  She has club activities.
I wonder what I'll eat today?
美也　今日　何食べようかなあ
アイス　のっけちゃおうかな
Maybe I'll have ice cream with it!
え～ッ　こんなに寒いのに？
Really?  It's so cold though.
美也ちゃん　どうかしたの？
Miya-chan, what's wrong?
うちのお兄ちゃんがいたから
えッ？
My brother's right there.
Huh?
So he's your brother, Miya-chan...
あの人が美也ちゃんのお兄さん…
行こう！
えッ　いいの？　お兄さん
Let's go!
But your brother... are you sure?
うん
どうせ家でいつも会ってるしね～
Yep.
We see each other at home all the time anyway.
I-I see.
そッ　そう…
All right, I think I'll have salmon and wieners with it!
よーし　美也
サーモンとウィンナーつけちゃおっと
For pedestrians
and bikes
Well, I might be in it for the money,
あッ　でもね
目的は　お金かもしれないけど
ケッコー働くのって
おもしろいのよね
but the work itself is pretty fun.
へえ～　そうなんだ
うん
Oh, really?
Yeah.
お客さんに　ありがとうって
言われたりすると
It makes me happy when customers show me their appreciation.
これが　うれしいもんなのよ
なるほどね
I see.
あんたも一度
やってみるといいかもね
You should probably give it a try too.
You, with an apron over your uniform... it'll probably look good on you!
制服にエプロン姿　似合うかも
はあ　何で僕がエプロン？
Why would I be in an apron?
Anyway, you should come as a customer first.
とにかく　まずは
お客さんで来なさい
気が向いたらな
I'll come when I feel like it.
I'll give you some freebies...
サービス　し・て・あ・げ…　ないッ！
...not!
You won't?!
しないのかよ！？
Well, I'm headed this way.
じゃあ　私　こっちだから
あのさ　薫
うん？
Hey, Kaoru.
今日　花壇に呼び出されたとき
When you told me to come to the flower beds today,
I thought you were gonna confess to me.
僕　薫に
告白されるのかと思っちゃったよ
えッ
なわけないのにな
But there's no way that would happen.
勘違いにも　ほどがあるよな
Even if I'm getting the wrong idea, I shouldn't go too far.
ははは…
何か　薫にパンチ食らって
おかしくなってたのかな？
Maybe your punch made me a little crazy, Kaoru.
In that case, it's partly your fault too.
だったら
薫にも責任あるんだからな
薫？
Kaoru?
There's no way that'd happen!
なわけないじゃん
バッカじゃないの！？
Are you stupid?!
イッテ～
もう　さっさとバイト行かなきゃ
Ow...
Geez, I have to get to my job...
遅刻　遅刻
I'll be late, late!
Come on, I said I got the wrong idea.
だから　勘違いって言ってるのに
たたかなくても…
You didn't have to hit me.
制服か…
Uniform, huh?
Sign: Café Restaurant Totosu
いやいや　そんなわけない！
No, no.  There's no way!
All right, time to work hard!
シャーッ！
さあ　今日も働くわよ！
よッ　早速来てやったぞ
Yo.  I decided to come right away.
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome.
Didn't I already say you won't be getting any freebies?
サービスしないって言ったでしょ
えッ？
ご注文は？
What would you like?
I'll leave it to you.  Something cheap.
お任せ　安いので
えっと…
Let's see, the cheapest item.
一番安い　コーヒーでいいわね？
How about coffee?  Refills are free.
お代わり自由だし
うん　それ以上だと難しい
Yeah, I don't think I can pay for anything pricier.
You're a coward.
弱気ね
ステーキとか　バーンと頼みなさいよ
You should just go all out and order a steak or something.
How about the "Crab From The North Gratin" from our Winter Flavors fair menu?
冬の味覚フェアの「北からきた
カニグラタン」とか　いかがですか？
あははッ
あの運びにくいやつか？
You mean that hard to carry item?
I see.
〈なるほど…〉
うん？
Wait, where do you think you're looking?!
ちょっと　どこ見てんのよ！？
W-Well, I'm not...
いッ　いや…　別に
やらしいわね
You pervert.
No, I definitely wasn't looking in a perverted way...
いや　決して　いやらしい視線で
見ているわけではなくて
ご注文は以上で　よろしいですか？
Is that all for you today?
Yes, thank you.
はい　よろしくお願いします
ふんッ！
Excuse me.
すみませ～ん
はい
Yes.
・（客）コーヒーのお代わり
お願いします
I'd like some more coffee, please.
かしこまりました
Understood.
Here you go.
お待たせしました
（女性客）うわッ！
あッ　すみません！
I'm sorry!
Please enjoy.
ごゆっくりどうぞ
What... what's happening?
何？　何　これ
まさか　私
Don't tell me I...
私　あいつに…
I... like...
This morning too, when I punched him...
〈今朝　あいつを殴ったのも〉
Ayatsuji-san has to live up to her role as the class rep.
《絢辻さんにもクラス委員って
立場があるんだからさ》
〈て　あいつが絢辻さんをかばう
ようなこと言うから…　それに〉
It's because he said it like he was protecting Ayatsuji-san.
Also...
《僕　薫に告白されるのかと
思っちゃったよ》
I thought you were gonna confess to me, Kaoru.
〈あんなこと言うから
何か　ドキドキが止まんなくて〉
My heart won't stop thumping because he said that...
うそ～ッ！
No way!
Here's your coffee.
（店員）コーヒー　お待たせしました
あッ　どうも
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
ごゆっくり　どうぞ
〈薫　どうしたのかな？〉
What happened to Kaoru?
〈もう一回　からかってから帰ろう
と思ってたのにな〉
I was hoping to tease her one more time before heading back.
・～
Naze naze
なぜ　なぜ
Why, oh why?
My Heart kurushii no
マイハート　苦しいの
Why does my heart ache like this?
Daijoubu nante ne
「大丈夫」 なんてね
I tell you that everything's fine
Sokkenai furi shitari
素っ気ないフりしたり
And behave coldly
Namaiki mo urahara
ナマイキも　うらはら
I act outrageous and disagreeable
Saidaigen no tsuyogari
最大限の強がり
It's the ultimate bluff
Doushite kana namida dechau
どうしてかな  ナミダ出ちゃう
Why am I starting to cry?
Aitsu no kao matomo ni mirenai
あいつの顔  まともに見れない
あいつの顔　まともに見れない
I can't even look squarely at his face
Ashita wa kitto kinou yori
明日はきっと　昨日より
Tomorrow for sure, even more than yesterday
Tomodachi ijou no kankei ni naritai
友達以上の関係になりたい
I want us to become more than just friends
Ashita wa kitto yume mo kitto
明日はきっと  夢もきっと
明日はきっと　夢もきっと
Tomorrow for sure, and in my dreams for sure
Koi suru kimochi kirameku
恋する気持ち　キラメク
These feelings of love will shine brilliantly
Just A Friend
Such A Friend
Still A Friend
Naze naze
なぜ　なぜ
Why, oh why?
I Can't Tell You My Heart
Why can't I tell you what's in my heart?
Preview
Next episode preview.
Oh?  What are you staring at with that huge grin on your face?
Morishima-senpai?!
Hey, hey.  What were you looking at?
I guess you could say I was captivated by the pristine sight of a devoted girl working hard at her part-time job.
Or you could say that I looked without thinking...
I just couldn't help it, being a guy...
Aha, so you were captivated by her thighs!
Next episode: "Hesitation".
Next Episode
Hesitation
Where, where?
Where's the girl with such sexy thighs?
Uh... Senpai?